<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mine | A. O Amao</title>
    <link>https://hammao.github.io/tags/mine/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://hammao.github.io/tags/mine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>mine</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© A. O Amao, 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://hammao.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>mine</title>
      <link>https://hammao.github.io/tags/mine/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>new post</title>
      <link>https://hammao.github.io/post/new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hammao.github.io/post/new-post/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lcolladotor.github.io/2018/03/07/blogdown-insert-image-addin/#.Xf6mB9lRXmE&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://lcolladotor.github.io/2018/03/07/blogdown-insert-image-addin/#.Xf6mB9lRXmE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;n Hugo, themes control the entire appearance and functionality of your site. So, if you care a lot about the appearance of your website, you will probably spend quite a bit of time in the beginning looking for a Hugo theme that you like from the collection listed at &lt;a href=&#34;http://themes.gohugo.io&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;http://themes.gohugo.io&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that not all themes have been tested against blogdown. If you find a certain theme does not work well with blogdown, you may report to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rstudio/blogdown/issues&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://github.com/rstudio/blogdown/issues&lt;/a&gt;, and we will try to investigate the reason, but it can be time-consuming to learn and understand how a new theme works, so we recommend that you learn more about Hugo by yourself before asking, and we also encourage users to help each other there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After you have found a satisfactory theme, you need to figure out its GitHub username and repository name,18 then either install the theme via blogdown::install_theme(), or just create a new site under another new directory and pass the GitHub repository name to the theme argument of new_site(). We recommend that you use the second approach, because Hugo themes could be very complicated and the usage of each theme can be very different and highly dependent on config.toml. If you install a theme using install_theme() instead of new_site() you’ll need to manually create the config.toml file in the root directory of your website to match the newly installed theme.19&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now use the Serve Site addin and check if you like your images. You might want to change the height/widths or alternate text. You could also wrap the HTML/Markdown code around it for linking to a website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also delete your original images, if for example, they are cluttering your&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://hammao.github.io/post/2019-12-22-new-post_files/index.jpeg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
